DELIVERANCE TIME
During the Sunday live service at the SCOAN, Wiseman Christopher ministers prayer
in the power of the Holy Ghost to the people.
As he ministers spirit-filled prayer, every chain satan has used to connect the people to himself
is being disconnected in Jesus' name.
You can see the reaction of the people as Wiseman Christopher ministers prayer in Jesus' name.
The demons that are the cause of their problems are being exposed and removed in Jesus' name.
Get ready to watch what happens when Wiseman Christopher encounters this man.
Don't come to me!
Why?
I don’t want to see a man like you!
You don’t want to see a man like me?
I said I'm serious about this!
Now, bring down your hand.
We don't carry on missions that we cannot finish.
I must surely finish what I started.
Who are you?
I don’t know if you can do yours.
What is your mission?
Follow me.
You!
I know who you are!
This is the time!
Time to do what?
I'm going to show you my last power!
What is the power all about?
I destroy.
I kill.
I fornicate.
I disturb the peace of the people.
Nobody ever questioned me. How dare you?!
Let me tell you what you don't know.
This one is our own.
Which one?
We have destroyed so many of them.
But the Lord wants to save this one.
He cannot!
I knew that a day like this would come, when I would meet you one on one.
What other evil have you done?
We don’t and we can never work like children!
We are matured in the realm.
Which realm?
You don’t know?
You want to tell me you don’t know?
Jesus knows.
The name we don’t want to hear.
Get out!
Why?
You said you don’t want to hear the name of Jesus, why?
See!
You may be holding me
but let me tell you, you are not as strong as this man!
Stop that!
Stop that and answer me, you demon.
What is the evil you have done?
How did you enter this man's body?
Through many ways!
Like what?
In the dream!
We fed him many years ago in his dreams!
He is married to a wife in the spirit.
Do you think that you can take the wife away from him?
Though his future is bright, I don’t know if you can do that!
If you think you can, let's get to the battleground!
What other evil have you done?
Don't frustrate me!
I told you!
Or, you think I'm joking with you?
I know you are a man of God
but the power...
My last power – I will use it to fight the last battle, if this is the one.
What do you mean by the last battle?
The last mission in my life.
If I don’t destroy him, then the victory is yours.
How do you want to go about destroying him?
I know the family background.
What have you done to the family?
I know what they did in the family, before they gave birth to him.
They would have killed the mother
but God loves the mother and the son.
Both the parents are dead and the son will not live.
What did you do to the family?
Go and ask them in the village!
We almost finished the family!
The family is a family of ten, but it is only four that survived.
What happened to the other six?
Don’t question me, I told you!
How dare you to question a man like me?!
I said I'm strong in the realm.
That's why you see me today.
Let's get to the battleground!
I know you are one of the heads.
Are you not?
You want me to tell you all about you?
I'm just waiting for the last bell to ring, then the battle will begin.
What do you mean by the battle?
You cannot just cast a spirit out of a human without a fight.
It is a struggle!
Let's make it 50/50.
Do you know what I mean by that?
Go ahead and explain.
One of your body parts will be destroyed for you to save this one.
You think I'm joking, right?
Are you now ready for the battle?
Of course, yes!
Are you strong enough to withstand me? Then let's try it!
The battle for survival is not a personal challenge, but one against Jesus.
Are you ready?
Don't fight with me, please!
You said what?
I will call he who is stronger than me to fight you, right now!
Are you now ready to fight?
Yes, I am.
Can you stand right and get ready? Position yourself!
Get ready. Is there any other thing you need to do?
Are you getting ready?
I command fire from Heaven.
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Holy Ghost fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out, you demon!
Out!
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire in the name of Jesus!
Fire in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire!
Help me!
Fire in the name of Jesus Christ!
No hiding place!
You cannot go beyond the Word of God, come back!
Come back here in the name of Jesus Christ!
Come!
Didn’t I tell you?
It would be 50/50 today!
Now, stop!
Are you still ready to fight?
Stop!
Come back, in the name of Jesus Christ!
At the count of three!
Didn’t I tell you?
Are you ready to lose one of your hands for him to be free?
Stop there!
I stopped.
That means I have surrendered but I can't just surrender.
I want to see more of your power.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out, in the name of Jesus!
Come out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
At the mention of the name "Jesus Christ" all knees shall bow.
Now go.
No!
What can I do for you to allow me? |
Go.
No, because we don’t have anywhere to go.
I command you to go.
Move.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Stop!
Where are you going?
Come back.
Come back here.
Allow me to be myself, but until the shoes are removed…
Holy Ghost fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
Pity me, please.
Go back to where you are coming from.
But this is the only home I have.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out of him.
Come back here!
Holy Ghost fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire!
What did you say?
What is happening now?
Where am I?
Tell me please!
Come here!
The Lord has set you free; relax.
Are you sure? Am I safe?
What is this?
Calm down.
What is happening here? Look at my clothes.
You said you were a demon.
That you possessed this body.
And you had a mission and your mission was in three categories -
to kill, to steal and to destroy.
No.
You destroyed a lot of people and you wanted to kill this brother.
They had ten people in the family and you succeeded in killing six;
only four remain now.
I only knew that there were a lot of problems in my family.
Almost all of my brothers are dead.
My parents are dead.
Even me, nothing is in place at all.
Sometimes, I think I should go drink poison and die.
There was a day, I was watching Emmanuel TV,
people were receiving miracles, in a restaurant where I went to eat.
I thought that one day I would visit the church and God would help me.
And here you are. Lord has cast out...
Praise the Lord!
Thank You, Jesus!
I know I'm free!
I am free!
Thank You, Jesus! I am free!
In Jesus' name, I am free forever!